Guide to the Montana State College, Office of the President Annual Reports Received 1921-1968
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
Montana State College, Office of the President Annual Reports Received
1921-1968
Montana State University-Bozeman Library, Merrill G Burlingame Special Collections P.O. Box 173320 Bozeman, MT 59717-3320 United States Phone (406) 994-4242 Fax (406) 994-2851 http://www.lib.montana.edu/archives/ University Archivist spcoll@www.lib.montana.edu
Accession 12002, MtBC, us
Montana State College. Office of the President.
10 linear feet
The Montana State College, Office of the President Annual Reports Received comprise a collection of prepared statements created by various academic and administrative subdivisions of the school from 1921 to 1968, the bulk of which were issued prior to the 1965 establishment of the school as a university. These subdivisions include academic departments, schools, divisions, and colleges, along with academic support units such as the registrar and student health center.
Biographical Note
Montana State University (MSU) was founded in 1893 as the state's land-grant college, and named the Agricultural College of the State of Montana. Later renamed the Montana College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts, by the 1920s it was commonly referred to as Montana State College (MSC). Recognizing the institution's growth and excellence in undergraduate and graduate education, the state assembly renamed the institution Montana State University on 1 July 1965. Although the school was consistently overseen by an appointed president since its founding, MSU's various subdivisions have been renamed and reorganized numerous times. This is especially true for the various colleges, which prvious to 1965 were referred to at different times as "schools" or "divisions." These various academic subunits were sometimes headed by a person designated as either a director or a dean. The date of establishment for each of the colleges that presently comprise MSU, partially based on their designation of the academic unit's head as a "dean," are: College of Agriculture, 1915; College of Arts and Architecture, 1976, College of Business, 1984; College of Education, Health, and Human Development, 1987; College of Engineering, 1915; College of Letters and Science, 1960; College of Nursing, 1984; Gallatin College, 2010; University College, 2008.
The MSU President's office annual reports recieved comprise a collection of prepared statements created by various academic and administrative subdivisions of the school from 1921 to 1968, the bulk of which were issued prior to the 1965 establishment of the school as a university. These subdivisions include academic departments, schools, divisions, and colleges, along with acadmic support units such as the registrar and student health center. The reports generally give an overview of the given year's activities by faculty and staff. Information includes the performance of teaching and teaching support work, grants and other financial data, and occasionally indvidual employees and their activities. Not all units are represented in the files, and the chronological coverage varies. The reports have been placed in alphabetical order by the name of the academic or administrative subgroup and then chronologically afterwards.
This collection is open for research.
Annual reports created by departments, colleges, divisions, and other offices of Montana State Unviersity and sent to the president's office were isolated for research use sometime during the 1980s and assigned their current accession number in August 2012.
Montana State College -- Administration; Montana State College -- Presidents; Montana State College -- Students; Montana State University (Bozeman, Mont.) -- Administration; Montana State University (Bozeman, Mont.) -- Presidents; Montana State University (Bozeman, Mont.) -- Students; Montana State College; Montana State University (Bozeman, Mont.)
Montana State University (Bozeman, Mont.). Office of the President
Montana -- Economic conditions -- 20th century; Montana
Agriculture and state -- Montana; Education -- Montana; Education, Higher -- Montana; Schools -- Montana; Agriculture and state; Economic history; Education; Education, Higher; Management; Presidents; Schools; Students
Agriculture; Architecture; Colleges and Universities; Economics and Banking; Elementary and Secondary Education; Fine Arts; Language and Languages; Medicine and Health; Military; Music; Science; Montana
Annual reports -- Montana -- Bozeman
- Admissions, Office of, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 1/1)
- Admissions, Office of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 1/2)
- Agricultural Economics, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 1/3)
- Agricultural Economics, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 1/4)
- Agricultural Economics, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 1/5)
- Agricultural Economics, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 1/6)
- Agricultural Economics, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 1/7)
- Agricultural Economics, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 1/8)
- Agricultural Economics, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 1/9)
- Agricultural Economics, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 1/10)
- Agricultural Economics, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 1/11)
- Agricultural Economics, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 1/12)
- Agricultural Economics, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 1/13)
- Agricultural Economics, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 1/14)
- Agricultural Economics, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 1/15-16)
- Agricultural Economics, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 1/17)
- Agricultural Economics, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 1/18)
- Agricultural Economics, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 1/19)
- Agricultural Economics, 1929/1930-1936/1937 (Box-folder 1/20)
- Agricultural Economics, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 1/21)
- Agricultural Economics, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 1/22-23)
- Agricultural Economics, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 1/24)
- Agricultural Economics, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 1/25)
- Agricultural Economics, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 1/26)
- Agricultural Economics, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 1/27)
- Agricultural Economics, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 1/28)
- Agricultural Economics, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 1/29)
- Agricultural Economics, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 1/30)
- Agricultural Economics, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 1/31)
- Agricultural Economics, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 1/32)
- Agricultural Economics, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1/33)
- Agricultural Economics, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 1/34)
- Agricultural Economics, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 1/35)
- Agricultural Economics, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 1/36)
- Agricultural Economics, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 1/37)
- Agricultural Economics, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 1/38)
- Agricultural Economics, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 1/39)
- Agricultural Economics, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 1/40)
- Agricultural Experiment Station, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 1/41)
- Agricultural Experiment Station, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 1/42)
- Agriculture Animal Husbandry, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 1/43)
- Agriculture Animal Husbandry, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 1/44)
- Agriculture Animal Husbandry, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 1/45)
- Agriculture Irrigation and Drainage, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 1/46)
- Agriculture Irrigation and Drainage, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 1/47-48)
- Agriculture Irrigation and Drainage, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 1/49)
- Agriculture-Vice Dean, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 1/50)
- Agriculture-College of, 1929-1934 (Box-folder 1/51)
- Agriculture-School of, 1928/1929-1935/1936 (Box-folder 1/52)
- Agriculture-School of, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 1/53)
- Agriculture, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 1/54)
- Agriculture, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 1/55)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 1/56)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 1/57)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 1/58)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 1/59)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 1/60)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 1/61)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 1/62)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 1/63)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 1/64)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 1/65)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 1/66)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 1/67)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1/68)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 1/69)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 1/70)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 1/71)
- Agronomy and Soils, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 1/72)
- Division of Agriculture, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 1/73)
- Division of Agriculture, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 1/74)
- Division of Agriculture, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 1/75)
- Division of Agriculture, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 1/76)
- Division of Agriculture, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 1/77)
- Division of Agriculture, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 1/78)
- Division of Agriculture, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 1/79)
- Division of Agriculture, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 1/80)
- Division of Agriculture, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 1/81)
- Division of Agriculture, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1/82)
- Division of Agriculture, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 1/83)
- Division of Agriculture, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 1/84)
- Division of Agriculture, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 1/85)
- Division of Agriculture, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 1/86)
- Division of Agriculture, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 1/87)
- Division of Agriculture, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 1/88)
- Air Force ROTC, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 1/89)
- Air Force ROTC, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 1/90)
- Air Force ROTC, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 1/91)
- Air Force ROTC, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 1/92)
- Air Force ROTC, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 1/93)
- Air Force ROTC, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 1/94)
- Air Force ROTC, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 1/95)
- Army ROTC, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 1/96)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 2/1)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 2/2)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 2/3)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 2/4)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 2/5)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 2/6)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 2/7)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 2/8)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 2/9)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/10)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 2/11)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 2/12)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 2/13)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1961 (Box-folder 2/14)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1961/1962 (Box-folder 2/15)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 2/16)
- Animal Industry and Range, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 2/17)
- Applied Art, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 2/18)
- Applied Art, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 2/19)
- Applied Art, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 2/20)
- Applied Art, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 2/21)
- Applied Art, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 2/22)
- Applied Art, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 2/23)
- Applied Art, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 2/24)
- Applied Art, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 2/25)
- Applied Art, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 2/26)
- Applied Art, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 2/27)
- Applied Art, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 2/28)
- Applied Art, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 2/29)
- Applied Art, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 2/30)
- Applied Art, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 2/31)
- Applied Art, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 2/32)
- Applied Art, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/33)
- Applied Art, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 2/34)
- Applied Art, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 2/35)
- Applied Art, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 2/36)
- Applied Art, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 2/37)
- Applied Art, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 2/38)
- Applied Art, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 2/39)
- Architecture, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 2/40)
- Architecture, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 2/41)
- Architecture, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 2/42)
- Architecture, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 2/43)
- Architecture, 1940-1944 (Box-folder 2/44)
- Architecture, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 2/45)
- Architecture, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 2/46)
- Architecture, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 2/47)
- Architecture, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 2/48)
- Architecture, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 2/49)
- Architecture, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 2/50)
- Architecture, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 2/51)
- Architecture, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 2/52)
- Architecture, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 2/53)
- Architecture, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/54)
- Architecture, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 2/55)
- Architecture, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 2/56)
- Architecture, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 2/57)
- Architecture, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 2/58)
- Architecture, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 2/59)
- Architecture, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 2/60)
- Architecture, 1958-59 (Box-folder 2/61)
- Architecture, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 2/62)
- Architecture, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 2/63)
- Architecture, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 2/64)
- Architecture -75th History, 1966 (Box-folder 2/65)
- The First 50 Years-History (Box-folder 2/66)
- Survey of Department Heads-75th History, 1950-1975 (Box-folder 2/67)
- Art, 1960/1961-1966/1967 (Box-folder 2/68)
- Art, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 2/69)
- Art, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 2/70)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 2/71)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 2/72)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 2/73)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 2/74)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 2/75)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 2/76)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 2/77)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 2/78)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 2/79)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 2/80)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 2/81)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 2/82)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 2/83)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 2/84)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 2/85)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/86)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 2/87)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 2/88)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 2/89)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 2/90)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 2/91)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 2/92)
- Botany and Bacteriology, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 2/93)
- Chemistry, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 2/94)
- Chemistry, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 2/95)
- Chemistry, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 2/96)
- Chemistry, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 2/97)
- Chemistry, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 2/98)
- Chemistry, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 2/99)
- Chemistry, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 2/100)
- Chemistry, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 2/101)
- Chemistry, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 2/102)
- Chemistry, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 2/103)
- Chemistry, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 2/104)
- Chemistry, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 2/105)
- Chemistry, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 2/106)
- Chemistry, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 2/107)
- Chemistry, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/108)
- Chemistry, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 2/109)
- Chemistry, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 2/110)
- Chemistry, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 2/111)
- Chemistry, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 2/112)
- Chemistry, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 2/113)
- Chemistry, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 2/114)
- Chemistry, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 2/115)
- Chemistry, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 2/116)
- Chemistry, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 2/117)
- Chemistry, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 2/118)
- Chemistry, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 2/119)
- Chemistry, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 2/120)
- Chemistry, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 2/121)
- Chemistry, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 2/122)
- Commercial Science, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 2/123)
- Commercial Science, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 2/124)
- Commercial Science, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 2/125)
- Commercial Science, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/126)
- Commercial Science, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 2/127)
- Commercial Science, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 2/128)
- Commercial Science, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 2/129)
- Commercial Science, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 2/130)
- Commercial Science, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 2/131)
- Commercial Science, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 2/132)
- Commercial Science, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 2/133)
- Commercial Science, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 2/134)
- Commercial Science, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 2/135)
- Standing Committee, 1942-1942 (Box-folder 3/1)
- Conservation Education, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 3/2)
- Conservation Education, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 3/3)
- Continuing Education, 1964 (Box-folder 3/4)
- Dairy Industry, 1929/1930-1936/1937 (Box-folder 3/5)
- Dairy Industry, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 3/6)
- Dairy Industry, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 3/7)
- Dairy Industry, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 3/8)
- Dairy Industry, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 3/9)
- Dairy Industry, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3/10)
- Dairy Industry, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 3/11)
- Dairy Industry, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 3/12)
- Dairy Industry, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 3/13)
- Dairy Industry, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 3/14)
- Dairy Industry, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 3/15)
- Dairy Industry, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 3/16)
- Dairy Industry, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/17)
- Dairy Industry, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 3/18)
- Dairy Industry, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 3/19)
- Dairy Industry, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 3/20)
- Dairy Industry, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 3/21)
- Dairy Research, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/22)
- Dean of the Faculty, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 3/23)
- Dean of the Faculty, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 3/24)
- Dean of the Faculty, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 3/25)
- Dean of the Faculty, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/26)
- Dean of the Faculty, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 3/27)
- Dean of the Faculty, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 3/28)
- Dean of the Faculty, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 3/29)
- Dean of Men, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 3/30)
- Dean of Men, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 3/31)
- Dean of Men, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 3/32)
- Dean of Men, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 3/33)
- Dean of Men, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 3/34)
- Dean of Students, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 3/35)
- Dean of Students, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 3/36)
- Dean of Students, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 3/37)
- Dean of Students, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 3/38)
- Dean of Students, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/39)
- Dean of Students, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 3/40-41)
- Dean of Students, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 3/42)
- Dean of Women, 1932/1933-1952/1953 (Box-folder 3/43)
- Dean of Women, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 3/44)
- Dean of Women, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 3/45)
- Dean of Women, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 3/46)
- Dean of Women, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 3/47)
- Dean of Women, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 3/48)
- Dean of Women, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 3/49)
- Dean of Women, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/50)
- Dean of Women, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 3/51)
- Dean of Women, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 3/52)
- Department Organizations, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/53)
- Economics and Sociology, 1929/1930-1936/1937 (Box-folder 3/54)
- Economics and Sociology, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 3/55)
- Economics and Sociology, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 3/56)
- Economics and Sociology, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 3/57)
- Economics and Sociology, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 3/58)
- Economics and Sociology, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 3/59)
- Economics and Sociology, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 3/60)
- Economics and Sociology, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 3/61)
- Economics and Sociology, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 3/62)
- Economics and Sociology, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 3/63)
- Economics and Sociology, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 3/64)
- Economics and Sociology, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/65)
- Economics and Sociology, 1952 (Box-folder 3/66)
- Economics and Sociology, 1952/1953 (Box-folder 3/67)
- Economics and Sociology, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 3/68-69)
- Economics and Sociology, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 3/70)
- Economics and Sociology, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 3/71)
- Economics and Sociology, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 3/72)
- Economics and Sociology, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 3/73)
- Economics and Sociology, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 3/74)
- Economics and Sociology, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/75)
- Education on Psychology, 1929-1937 (Box-folder 3/76)
- Education on Psychology, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 3/77)
- Education on Psychology, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 3/78)
- Education on Psychology, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 3/79)
- Education on Psychology, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 3/80)
- Education on Psychology, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 3/81)
- Education on Psychology, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3/82)
- Education on Psychology, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 3/83)
- Education on Psychology, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 3/84)
- Education on Psychology, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 3/85)
- Education on Psychology, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 3/86)
- Education on Psychology, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 3/87)
- Education on Psychology, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 3/88)
- Education on Psychology, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 3/89)
- Education on Psychology, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 3/90)
- Education on Psychology, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/91)
- Education on Psychology, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 3/92)
- Education on Psychology, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 3/93)
- Dean of Education (Box-folder 3/94)
- Dean of Education, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 3/95)
- Division of Education, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 3/96)
- Education, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 3/97)
- Dean of Education, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 3/98)
- Division of Education, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 3/99)
- Division of Education, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/100)
- Education, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/101)
- Education, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 3/102)
- Educational Research, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 3/103)
- Educational Research, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 3/104)
- Educational Research, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 3/105)
- Educational Research, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 3/106)
- Endowment and Research Foundation, 1959 (Box-folder 3/107)
- English, 1928/1929-1936/1937 (Box-folder 3/108)
- English, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 3/109)
- English, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 3/110)
- English, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 3/111)
- English, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 3/112)
- English, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 3/113)
- English, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3/114)
- English, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 3/115)
- English, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 3/116)
- English, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 3/117)
- English, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 3/118)
- English, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 3/119)
- English, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 3/120)
- English, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 3/121)
- English, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 3/122)
- English, 1952 (Box-folder 3/123)
- English, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 3/124)
- English, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 3/125)
- English, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 3/126)
- English, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 3/127)
- English, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 3/128)
- English, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 3/129)
- English, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/130)
- Experiment Station (Box-folder 3/131)
- Faculty, Individual, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 3/132)
- Family Housing Project, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 3/133)
- Family Housing Project, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 3/134)
- Family Housing Project, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 3/135)
- Family Housing Project, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 3/136)
- Fellowships and Scholarships Committee, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 3/137)
- Film and Television, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 3/138)
- Film and Television, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 3/139)
- Film and Television, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 3/140)
- Foreign Student and Scholarships, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 3/141)
- General Division, 1934/1935-1936/1937 (Box-folder 3/142)
- Geography and Geology, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/1)
- Geography and Geology, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/2)
- Geography and Geology, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/3)
- Geography and Geology, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/4)
- Geography and Geology, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4/5)
- Geography and Geology, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/6)
- Geography and Geology, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 4/7)
- Geography and Geology, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 4/8)
- Geography and Geology, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 4/9)
- Geography and Geology, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/10)
- Geography and Geology, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/11)
- Geography and Geology, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 4/12)
- Geography and Geology, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/13)
- Graduate Studies, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 4/14)
- Graduate Studies, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/15)
- Graduate Studies, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4/16)
- Graduate Studies, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/17)
- Graduate Studies, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/18)
- Graduate Studies, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/19)
- Graduate Studies, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/20)
- Graduate Studies, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4/21)